##### Main navigation

* Locations
    * Alabama
    * California
    * Florida
    * Georgia
    * Indiana
    * Kentucky
    * Massachusetts
    * Michigan
    * New York
    * Nevada
    * North Carolina
    * Pennsylvania
    * South Carolina
    * Tennessee
    * Texas
* Practice Areas
    * Car Accidents
    * Personal Injury
    * Medical Malpractice
    * Negligence
    * Workplace
    * Civil Rights
    * Class Actions
    * Dangerous Drugs
    * Data Breach
    * Defective Products
    * Disaster Recovery
    * Insurance Disputes
    * Mass Arbitration
    * Mass Tort
    * Toxics and Environmental
* About
    * Careers

Popular Topics

Search
------

Use this form to search the site. Enter your search query and press enter to search.

877-667-4265 Call Now - Open 24/7 877-667-4265

MORGAN & MORGAN, P.A. PRIVACY POLICY
====================================

Morgan & Morgan, P.A. and its affiliates (referred to herein as “MM”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to complying with this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”), which describes what personal information we collect about you, how we use it, to whom we may disclose it, and what choices you have regarding our use of your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to personal information collected in connection with our website located at [www.forthepeople.com](https://www.forthepeople.com/) and any other webpage that MM maintains that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Site”), any current or future mobile applications associated with MM or the Site (collectively, the “App”), our email communications, our social media pages, other online or wireless offerings that post a link to the Privacy Policy, and other circumstances in connection with the services we provide (collectively, the “Platform”).   

This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:

TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
----------------------------------------

The types of personal information we collect will depend on the services you request and, if you are a client, the nature of our representation or your case. The table below describes the categories (with non-exhaustive examples) of personal information we may collect about you. We may also collect other personal information that is not specifically listed here, which we will use as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection. 

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Categories** | **Examples** |
| **Individual Identifiers and Demographic Information** | **Contact information,** such as name, email address, phone number, mailing address, job title, and organization.  <br>**Identifiers,** such as client ID, username, IP address, device ID, and other online identifiers that may be collected automatically when you use the Platform.  <br>**Demographic information,** such as date of birth, gender, age, marital status, and race pulled from your claim. |
| **Sensitive Personal Information** | **Government ID numbers,** such as Social Security number, driver’s license number, passport number, and other identification information.  <br>Financial information, such as financial account numbers, wiring instructions, insurance policy numbers, invoices, and other payment or bank account details.  <br>**Medical information,** such as doctor’s notes, treatment plans, medical conditions, prescription medicines, insurance documentation, doctor visit information, daily symptom reporting, and other records and information.  <br>**Precise physical location,** which we may collect via the App if you consent to that collection through the App. |
| **Sensory Data** | **Call recordings,** such as our recordings of calls you make to our customer service team, which may be recorded by us and our service providers.  <br>**Other sensory data,** such as any audio recordings, photographs, videos, or similar data that may be provided as part of a case file. |
| **Commercial Information** | **Representation information,** such as details about your claim, case, or other legal matter,  the distribution of settlement of other payments to you (if applicable).  <br>**Account information,** such as the username and password you provide when you register for an account and any information stored or transmitted in your account or profile.  <br>**Communications,** such as when you call or email us, confidential and privileged communications that you may make with our attorneys, and your conversations with our digital chat services (which may be recorded by us and our service providers). |
| **Internet or Network Activity** | **Online activity information,** such as linking pages, pages or screens viewed, time spent on a page or screen, navigation paths between pages or screens, information about activity on a page or screen, access times, duration of access, and other online activity information.  <br>**Device information,** such as computer and mobile operating system, operating system type and version number, wireless carrier, manufacturer and model, browser type, screen resolution, general location information such as city, state, or geographic area, and other device information collected automatically. |
| **Inferences Drawn from Personal Information** | **Profiles** reflecting preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, or aptitudes. |

We may collect the categories of personal information described above from the following sources:

* **Personal Information You Provide Us.** We collect the personal information that you provide to us while using our Platform, including contacting us, creating an account, or otherwise. Further, where expressly designated by MM, some portions of the Services may be used by active MM clients to communicate pursuant to an attorney/client relationship. You may choose whether or not to provide such information; however, the information may be required to respond to your request.
* **Personal Information Collected Automatically.** We and our third party providers may use cookies and other technologies to collect personal information about you automatically when you use our Platform. Such information includes the online identifiers, device information, and online activity information described above.   
      
    To facilitate the automatic collection described above, we may use the following technologies:

* **Cookies**. A cookie is a small piece of data stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device. We use cookies to collect information from you regarding your usage of the Platform in order to remember user preferences and settings, personalize your experience with the Platform, facilitate online advertising, and for security purposes. You may opt-out of the automatic collection of some information by referring to your web browser or mobile device options or settings menu. However, doing so may disable many of the portions, features, or functionality of the Platform. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences or visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) for more information.
* **Pixels**. Pixels, which are also known as “web beacons,” or “clear GIFs,” are typically used to determine whether a webpage or email was accessed or opened, or that certain content was viewed or clicked. Data collected from pixels is often used to compile statistics about usage of websites and the success of email marketing campaigns.
* **SDKs**. Software development kits, or “SDKs,” are third-party computer codes used in connection with the App for a variety purposes, including to provide analytics regarding the use of the App, integrate with social media, add features or functionality to the App, or facilitate online advertising. SDKs may enable third parties to collect information directly via the App.
* **Session Replay Technologies.** Session-replay technologies are third-party software used to record a video replay of users’ interactions with the Site. The video replay may include users’ clicks, mouse movements, scrolls, mobile app touches, typing, and other activity taken during the session. We use these replays for research and development purposes, such as to help us troubleshoot problems with the Site, understand how users interact with and use the Site, and identify areas for improvement.
* **Local storage.**  Local storage is used to save data on a visitor’s device. We use data from local storage to turn on web navigation, store multimedia preferences, customize what we show you based on your past interactions with our services, remember your preferences, and measure ad effectiveness.  

* **Personal Information Collected from Third Parties.** We may also collect or receive personal information from third parties, which may include:

* **Our business partners**, such as third-party data providers, advertising partners, and service providers.
* **Public sources**, such as social media platforms and publicly available records.
* **Individuals or entities involved in our clients’ legal matters**, such as doctors, other parties, and other individuals that you may direct to provide us with information.
* **Referral sources**, such as members of our referral network, website submissions, and other referral sources.  

We may merge or combine such personal information with the personal information we collect from you directly or automatically.

ONLINE ANALYTICS
----------------

We may use third party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics and Mouseflow, in order to better understand your use of our Platform and how we can improve them. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit and other usage information. For more information regarding how Google collects, uses, and shares your information please visit [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). For more information on Mouseflow’s privacy practices, please visit [https://mouseflow.com/legal/company/privacy-policy/](https://mouseflow.com/legal/company/privacy-policy/). To prevent data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the opt-out browser add-on at: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). You can opt out of Mouseflow analytics at: [https://mouseflow.com/opt-out/](https://mouseflow.com/opt-out/).  

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
---------------------------

We may use the personal information we collect for the following purposes and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:

* **To Provide Our Platform**. We use personal information to provide our services, including the Platform. For example, we use personal information:

* to facilitate your requests for a free case evaluation and determine your legal needs;
* to provide you with legal and other services, content, and features you request;
* to create, manage, and monitor your account;
* to respond to your inquiries and communicate with you, including placing calls or sending texts using any automated technology, including prerecorded messages;
* to operate, troubleshoot, and improve the Platform;
* to process your transactions, invoices, and settlement payments;
* to understand your interests, personalize your experience on the Platform, and deliver information about products and services relevant to your interests; 
* respond to your inquiries and requests for customer support, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses; and
* enable security features of the Platform, such as by sending you security codes via email or SMS, and remembering devices from which you have previously logged in.   

* **For Direct Marketing.** We may use your personal information to send you newsletters, legal updates, event information, marketing communications, and other information that may interest you. You may opt-out of our marketing communications as described in the “Your Choices” section below.
* **For Research and Development**. We use personal information for research and development purposes and to understand how people are using the Platform, including by generating and analyzing statistics, preferences, and usage trends, to make our Platform and other offerings better, diagnose technical issues, and develop new features and functionality. As part of these activities, we may create aggregated, de-identified or other anonymous data from personal information we collect. We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Platform and promote our business. 
* **For Compliance, Fraud Prevention and Safety**.

* to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements we may have;
* to comply with applicable laws, regulations, lawful requests, and legal processes;
* to protect our, your, or others’ rights, privacy, safety, or property (including by making and defending legal claims);
* to maintain the security and integrity of our business, the Platform, users, our third party business partners and service providers, our databases and other technology assets;
* audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements and internal policies; and
* prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.

* **For Interest-Based Advertising.** We, our service providers, and our third party advertising partners may collect and use your personal information for advertising purposes. We may contract with third-party advertising companies and social media companies to help us advertise our services, identify potential customers, and display ads on our Platform and other sites and services, including through the use of interest-based advertising. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about you (including the device information and online activity information described above) over time across our Platform and other sites and services or your interaction with our emails, and use that information to serve ads that they think will interest you and/or use hashed customer lists that we share with them to deliver ads to you and to similar users on their sites and services. You can learn more about your choices for limiting interest-based advertising, under “Advertising Choices” in the “Your Choices” section below.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
----------------------------------

In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise described at the time of collection, we may disclose personal information with the following categories of recipients:

* **Service Providers.** MM may share your personal information with third-party service providers that perform services for us or on our behalf, such as web-hosting companies, mailing vendors, analytics providers, event hosting services, and information technology providers. These third-party service providers have limited access to personal information as needed to perform their functions on our behalf and for no other purpose. MM will not share with third-party service providers any text message originator opt-in data and consent, or any election to receive SMS communications.
* **Other Law Firms or Lawyers.** MM may share, at your direction or with your permission, your personal information with other law firms and/or other lawyers where we jointly represent a client and when we refer cases or potential cases to other counsel, or as otherwise required in connection with our legal representation of you. Personal information provided pursuant to an attorney/client relationship may not be shared with third parties except as is done with such precautions to preserve the confidentiality of such information and any attorney/client privilege as may attach to such information.
* **Authorities, Law Enforcement, and Private Parties.** MM may disclose personal information to comply with laws, regulations or other legal obligations, to assist in an investigation, to protect and defend our rights and property, or the rights or safety of third parties, to enforce our agreements, Terms of Use or agreements with third parties, or for crime-prevention purposes.
* **Business Transactions.** MM may disclose your personal information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a transaction (or potential transaction) such as a corporate divestiture, financing, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization, sale, spin-off, or other disposition of all or any portion of the business or assets of, or equity interests in, MM or our related companies (including in connection with a bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
* **Advertising Partners.** We may share your personal information with third party advertising or joint marketing partners for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy (including interest-based advertising) or at the time of collection.
* **Professional Advisors**. We may disclose your personal information to our professional advisors, such as lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us.
* **Affiliates and Related Companies.** We may share your personal information with companies that are affiliated with us (that is, that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with us) or may be affiliated with us in the future for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
* **Consent**. MM may otherwise disclose your Personal Information in accordance with your prior direction or, in some cases, we may specifically ask you for your consent, such as when required by law.

YOUR CHOICES
------------

* **Opt-Out of Marketing Communications.** If you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can let us know by sending an email to [contact@forthepeople.com](mailto:contact@forthepeople.com) or by mail at the address provided below in the section called “Contact Us”. The electronic marketing communications we send may also contain an opt-out mechanism. Please note that it may take up to 10 calendar days to remove your contact information from our marketing communications lists, so you may receive correspondence from us for a short time after you make your request. Please also contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information that we have collected about you is inaccurate.
* **Text  Messages.** We may offer communications via SMS texts or similar technology sent by MM or our service providers, such as when we send you text messages for customer service, account-related, or marketing purposes. To stop receiving text messages from a short code operated by MM, reply STOP. Note that we may send you a message to confirm receipt of your STOP request. Message and data rates may apply for this service. You can also opt-out of MM marketing texts by emailing us your request and mobile telephone number to [contact@forthepeople.com](mailto:contact@forthepeople.com).
* **Cookies**. Most browsers let you remove or stop accepting cookies from the websites you visit. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser’s settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all functionality of the Platform and our Site may not work properly. For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your browser and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
* **Advertising Choices**. Some of our advertising partners are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and are subject to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising published by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can obtain more information about these companies’ information collection practices and opt-out of receiving interest-based advertising from participating NAI and DAA members at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp and/or the DAA’s website at optout.aboutads.info. You can also limit collection of your information for interest-based ads by blocking third party cookies in your browser settings or using privacy plug-ins or ad blocking software that help you block third party cookies. In addition, your mobile device settings may provide functionality to limit use of the advertising ID associated with your mobile device for targeted online advertising purposes. Some of the third party advertising companies we may work with offer their own opt-out options that you can use to limit their use of your information for interest-based advertising, such as Google (https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) and Facebook (https://www.facebook.com/about/ads),  or do not participate in the opt-out mechanisms described above. Many of the opt-out preferences described in this section must be set on each device and/or browser for which you want them to apply. If you opt-out of interest-based advertisements, you will still see advertisements online but they may be less relevant to you. Even after using these opt-out mechanisms, you may receive interest-based advertising from other companies.
* **“Do-Not-Track”.** Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a “Do Not Track” signal to the online services that you visit. At this time, the Site does not respond to a “Do Not Track” signal. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.
* **Declining to Provide Information**. We need to collect personal information to provide certain services. If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide those services.

INFORMATION SECURITY
--------------------

MM takes commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect the personal information we collect. Nevertheless, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information. Moreover, we are not responsible for the security of information you transmit to us over networks that we do not control, including the Internet and wireless networks.

LINKED WEBSITES
---------------

This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or social media features that may be accessed through links that we provide for your convenience and information. Accessing those links will cause you to leave MM’s website and may result in the collection of information about you by a third party. We do not control, endorse or make any representations about those third party websites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any site you interact with before allowing the collection and use of your information.

USING THE PLATFORM FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES
-------------------------------------------------

MM is headquartered in the United States of America, and we may have affiliates and service providers in the United States and other countries. Please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated, and other locations outside of your home country. The data protection and other laws of these countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using any portion of the Platform, you understand and, where applicable law permits, consent to the transfer of your personal information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties to whom we disclose it as described in this Privacy Policy.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
------------------

We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information online from children under the age of 18. Please contact us as provided below in the “Contact Us” section if you believe we may have collected such information.

ADDITIONAL NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF APPLICABLE U.S. STATES
--------------------------------------------------------

The following disclosures supplement the information provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy and apply to residents of certain U.S. states where local law requires us to provide additional information about our processing activities. For purposes of this section, “personal information” means “personal data” or “personal information” as such term is defined under applicable U.S. state privacy law but does not include information exempted from the scope of such law. 

Collection and Use of Personal Information

**We describe:**

* the categories of personal information we may collect, or have collected about you in the preceding 12 months, and the categories of sources from which we collect personal information in the section above called “Types of Personal Information We Collect”;
* the business and commercial purposes for which we process this information in the section above called “Use of Personal Information”; and
* the categories of third parties to whom we disclose this information in the section above called “Disclosure of Personal Information”.

**Personal Information We Disclose, “Sell,” “Share” or Use for “Targeted Advertising”**

Each of the categories of personal information described in the section above called “Types of Personal Information We Collect” may be disclosed, or has been disclosed in the 12 months preceding the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy, to the parties identified in the section above called “Disclosure of Personal Information” to operate our business or for another business purpose as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection.

Additionally, the following categories of personal information are, or in the 12 months preceding the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy have been, “sold” for monetary or other valuable consideration, “shared” for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes or disclosed or used for “targeted advertising” purposes, as those terms are defined under applicable state privacy law, to our Advertising Partners (described in the section above called “Disclosure of Personal Information”): Individual Identifiers and Demographic Information (such as name, email, IP address, device ID, other online identifiers, gender, age, and marital status) and Internet or Network Activity (each as further described in the section above called “Types of Personal Information We Collect”). To exercise your right to opt-out your personal information from such processing activities, please submit your request through the methods described under the “Exercising Your Privacy Rights” subsection below.

We do not knowingly “sell”, “share”, or use for “targeted advertising” the personal information of consumers we know to be less than 18 years of age.  

**Deidentified Information**

We may at times receive, or process personal information to create, deidentified data that can no longer reasonably be used to infer information about, or otherwise be linked to, a particular individual or household. Where we maintain deidentified data, we will maintain and use the data in deidentified form and not attempt to reidentify the data except as required or permitted by law.

**Retention of Personal Information**

We will only keep your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and processed, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, accounting, or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for your personal information, we will consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure, the purposes for which we process it (and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means), and the applicable legal requirements. In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal information so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case it is no longer personal information.

Depending on your residency and subject to certain legal limitations and exceptions, you may have certain rights relating to your personal information, such as the rights listed below. Please note, these rights may not apply in your jurisdiction, or may otherwise be limited by applicable law.

* **Right to Know**. The right to confirm whether we are processing personal information about you and to obtain certain details about the personal information we have collected about you, including, where applicable:  
    \- the categories of personal information collected;  
    \- the categories of sources from which we collected the personal information;  
    \- the purposes for which the personal information were collected;  
    \- the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties (if any), and the recipients to whom this personal information were disclosed;  
    \- the categories of personal information “sold” (if any), and the third parties to whom the personal information were sold; and  
    \- the categories of personal information shared for cross-context behavioral advertising or targeted advertising purposes (if any), and the categories of recipients to whom the personal information were disclosed for these purposes.

* **Right to Access & Portability.** The right to obtain access to the personal information we have collected about you and, where required by law, the right to obtain a copy of the personal information in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit the data to another entity without hindrance.
* **Right to Correction.** The right to correct inaccuracies in your personal information, taking into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of the processing of the personal information. 
* **Right to Deletion.** The right to request the deletion of personal information that we maintain about you, subject to certain exceptions.
* **Right to Opt-Out of “Sales.”** If we “sell” your personal information within the meaning of applicable U.S. state privacy law, you can request to opt-out of such sales. In most cases, a “sale” is defined as the disclosure of personal information to a third party for monetary consideration or, in some cases, for other valuable consideration.
* **Right to Opt-Out of “Sharing” or “Targeted Advertising.”** If we share or use your personal information for purposes of cross-context behavioral or targeted advertising within the meaning of applicable U.S. state privacy law, you can request to opt-out. 
* **Right to Revoke Consent or Limit the Use of Sensitive Data.** Where provided under applicable U.S. state privacy law, you have the right to revoke your consent or to request we limit the use or disclosure of your sensitive personal information to only certain business purposes set forth in applicable U.S. state privacy law.
* **Right to Non-Discrimination**. The right not to receive retaliatory or discriminatory treatment for exercising any of the rights described above. However, please note that if the exercise of the rights described above limits our ability to process personal information (such as in the case of a deletion request), we may no longer be able to provide you our services or engage with you in the same manner.  

**Exercising Your Privacy Rights**  
To request to exercise the privacy rights listed above where available under applicable law, please complete (or have your authorized agent complete) our interactive webform available by clicking here: Privacy Rights Portal, or call us toll-free at: 1-(844) 256-4550. 

If you wish to exercise your right to opt-out of “sales,” “sharing,” or “targeted advertising” as it relates to the use of cookies and other tracking technologies on our Site, please click the “Your Privacy Choices” link in the persistent footer of the Site. Where required by applicable law, the Site also recognizes the Global Privacy Control (GPC) signal. Note that due to technological limitations, if you visit our Site from a different computer or device, or clear cookies on your browser that store your preferences, you will need to return to the Site to select your preferences or rebroadcast the GPC signal.  

While we take measures to ensure that those responsible for receiving and responding to your request are informed of your rights and how to help you exercise those rights, when contacting us to exercise your rights, we ask you to please adhere to the following guidelines:

* **Tell Us Which Right You Are Exercising**: Specify which right you want to exercise and the personal information to which your request relates (if not to you).
* **Authorized Agents:** If you are an authorized agent acting on behalf of another consumer, please clearly indicate this fact and your authority to act on such consumer’s behalf. We may require the consumer’s proof of identification, the authorized agent’s proof of identification, and any other information that we may request in order to verify your request, including evidence of valid permission to act on the consumer’s behalf.
* **Help Us Verify Your Identity**: Provide us with information to verify your identity. Please note that if we cannot initially verify your identity and confirm you are a resident of a state that offers the relevant right(s), we may request additional information to complete the verification process. Any personal information you disclose to us for purposes of verifying your identity will solely be used for the purpose of verification.
* **Direct Our Response Delivery**: Please provide us with an e-mail or mailing address through which we can provide our response. If you make the request by email, unless otherwise requested, we will assume that we can respond to the email address from which you made the request.

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal information (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee or decline to comply with your request if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive, or excessive.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within 45 days of your request, or as otherwise required by applicable law. Occasionally it may take us longer than 45 days to respond, for instance if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this situation, we will notify you of the delay, and may continue to update you regarding the progress of our response.

**Appealing Privacy Rights Decisions**

Depending on your state of residency, you may be able to appeal a decision we have made in connection with a request you submit to us to exercise one of your privacy rights under applicable state privacy law. All appeal requests should be submitted by emailing us at contact@forthepeople.com with the subject line, “Privacy Request Appeal.” If you have concerns about the results of your appeal, depending on your state of residency, you have the ability to contact the Attorney General in your state.  

**Additional Notice to California Residents (Shine the Light)**  
If you are a California resident, we consider any request to opt-out of “sales” or “sharing” as a request pursuant to California’s “Shine the Light” law to stop sharing your personal information covered by that law with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Additional Notice to Nevada Residents**

Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A allows Nevada residents to opt-out of the “sale” of certain types of personal information. Subject to several exceptions, Nevada law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of certain types of personal information for monetary consideration to another person. If you are a Nevada resident who wishes to exercise your “sale” opt-out rights, you may submit a request to us using the contact information listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
------------------------------

MM may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices or in applicable law. Such changes will be effective upon posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Platform. You will be able to tell when this Privacy Policy was last updated by the Last Updated date included at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. By continuing to use our Platform, or communicating electronically with us thereafter, you acknowledge such changes to this Privacy Policy.

CONTACT US
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or MM’s information privacy practices, please contact us at:

E-mail: [contact@forthepeople.com](mailto:contact@forthepeople.com)

Telephone: [(407) 420-1414](tel:+14074201414)

Mail: Morgan & Morgan, PA, ATTN: Privacy Policy, 20 North Orange Ave, Suite 1600, Orlando, FL 32801

**LAST UPDATED**: September 1, 2024

Get a FREE case evaluation today
--------------------------------

As the largest personal injury law firm in America, Morgan & Morgan has recovered over $20 billion. Contact us today for a free case evaluation.

Free Case Evaluation
--------------------

Tell us about your situation so we can get started fighting for you. We tailor each case to meet our clients' needs.

First Name 

Last Name 

Phone Number 

Zip Code 

E-mail 

\- Case Type - \- Case Type -Airbag InjuryAnimal AttackBirth InjuryBusiness DisputeCar AccidentChildhood Sex AbuseCivil RightsClass ActionDangerous DrugsData BreachDefective ProductsEmployment IssueEnvironmental IssuesGardasilHair RelaxerHurt at WorkInsurance DisputeMaui WildfireMedical InjuryMesotheliomaNursing HomeOtherOther InjuryProduct InjurySlip & FallSocial Media HarmSocial SecurityTepezzaTrip and FallUnpaid Wages/EarningsVeteran DisabilityWeight Loss DrugWorkplace Discrimination

Please describe what happened

I hereby expressly consent to receive automated communications including calls, texts, emails, and/or prerecorded messages.  
  
By submitting this form, you agree to our [Terms](https://www.forthepeople.com/disclaimer-and-terms-of-use/) & acknowledge our [Privacy Policy](https://www.forthepeople.com/privacy-policy/).

           SUBMIT FORMFREE CASE EVALUATION

Extra info 

Results may vary depending on your particular facts and legal circumstances. ©2024 Morgan and Morgan, P.A. All rights reserved.

* ### About Us
    
* ### Resources
    
* ### Quick Links

### Social

20 North Orange Ave, Suite 1600, Orlando, FL 32801  
For a full list of locations in your area please visit our [Office Locations](https://www.forthepeople.com/office-locations/) page.

This site is designed to be accessible to and usable by people with and without disabilities. Please [contact us](https://www.forthepeople.com/complaints/) if you encounter an accessibility or usability issue on this site. Attorney advertising. Prior results do not guarantee a similar outcome.

Your privacy choices.

©2024 Morgan and Morgan, P.A. All rights reserved

Call Us Today - It's Free!877-667-4265
